This demo shows more than a diagnosis.
It shows the decision process.
We start with a real incident case.
H zero zero nine, liveness probe loop.
The service keeps restarting.
The liveness probe timing has drifted.
First, we run the case with a strict threshold profile.
The system explores a plausible path.
It scores that path.
It follows the available evidence.
But the confidence does not improve enough.
So this branch becomes a dead end.
That is important.
The failure is visible.
We can see where the path stalled.
We can see why it was rejected.
And we can backtrack.
Now we run the exact same case again.
Same problem.
Same signals.
But a different threshold profile.
This time, the system converges more cleanly.
So the goal is not only to produce an answer.
The goal is to make the reasoning explicit.
Reviewable.
And tunable.
Next, we switch to H zero zero six, network policy blocked.
Here, the system reaches a valid remediation path.
But it does not act automatically.
It stops at the human decision gate.
The operator reviews the recommendation.
Then chooses to approve or reject it.
That is the key point.
The system can explore.
Compare.
And justify decisions.
But the final operational choice remains under human control.